Guide to the University Archives photograph collection, 1861-ongoing UA.01.15.0009
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- People Series, 33 Boxes, approx. 16,500 items
  - James B. Duke Professors (Box 17)
  - James, Carl Clifton (Box 17)
  - James, Larry (Box 17)
  - James, Robert H. (Box 17)
  - Jayne, Benjamin (Box 17)
  - Jeffers, Katherine (Box 17)
  - Jennings, Ralph (Box 17)
  - Jensen, Howard (Box 17)
  - Johnson, Charles E. [Presbyterian Chaplain] (Box 17)
  - Johnson, Joseph (Box 17)
  - Johnson, Molly (Box 17)
  - Johnson, Terry (Box 17)
  - Joklik, Wolfgang Karl (Box 17)
  - Jones, Barney (Box 17)
  - Jones, Edward L., Sr. (Box 17)
  - Jones, Edward L., Jr. (Box 17)
  - Jones, J.A. (Box 17)
  - Jones, Randolph (Box 17)
  - Jones, William P. (Box 17)
  - Jordan, Queen of [Queen Noor Al Hussein] (Box 17)
  - Jordan, B. Everett (Box 17)
  - Jordan, Archibald (Box 17)
  - Jordan, Brady R. (Box 17)
  - Jordan, Charles Edward [Group Photos, including James C. Hagerty] (Box 17)
  - Jordan, Charles Edward [Portraits] (Box 17)
  - Jordan, L.R. (Box 18)
  - Jurgensen, Sonny (Box 18)
  - Kaiser, Helen (Box 18)
  - Kale, William Arthur (Box 18)
  - Kantner, George (Box 18)
  - Katzenbach, Nicholas De Belleville (Box 18)
  - Kaufman, N. (Box 18)
  - Kearns, Amos (Box 18)
  - Keech, J.M. (Box 18)
  - Kelly, Emmett, Jr. (Box 18)
  - Kempner, Walter (Box 18)
  - Kenan, William R. (Box 18)
  - Kennedy, John Fitzgerald (Box 18)
  - Kenyon, Van L. (Box 18)
  - Keohane, Nannerl, 1995 (Box 18)
  - Keohane, Nannerl (Box 18)
  - Keppell, Francis (Box 18)
  - Kerr, Clark (Box 18)
  - Kersten, Charles (Box 18)
  - Kilburn, Dr., 1969 [Cotton Brown Lint Story] (Box 18)
  - Kilgo, John Carlisle [Family and Group Photos], 2 folders (Box 18)
  - Killian, James R., Jr. (Box 18)
  - King, Martin Luther, Jr. (Box 18)
  - King, William E. (Box 18)
  - Kinney, Thomas (Box 18)
  - Klavins, Janis (Box 18)
  - Knight, Douglas M. [Portraits, Family] (Box 19)
  - Knight, Douglas M. [Inauguration], 2 folders (Box 19)
  - Knight, Douglas M. [Group Pictures], 2 folders (Box 19)
  - Knight, Grace (Mrs. Douglas M.) (Box 19)
  - Knight, Kenneth [Engineer, Class of 1933] (Box 19)
  - Koonz, Claudia (Box 19)
  - Kornberg, Dr. Allan (Box 19)
  - Korstian, Clarence Ferdinand (Box 19)
  - Koskinen, John (Box 19)
  - Kostyo, J. (Box 19)
  - Kraft, Chris (Box 19)
  - Kramer, Paul Jackson (Box 19)
  - Kramer, Robert (Box 19)
  - Kreps, Juanita (Box 19)
  - Krigbaum, William R. [Chemistry Department] (Box 19)
  - Krueger, Robert (Box 20)
  - Krzyzewski, Mike (Box 20)
  - Kubitschek, Juscelino (Box 20)
  - Kulski, Wladyslaw W. (Box 20)
  - Kunkle, Charles (Box 20)
  - Kurtz, Stanley (Box 20)
  - Kurzwell, Jeff (Box 20)
  - Kylstra, Johannes, 1965, 1968 [Physiology Department, Water Breathing] (Box 20)
  - La Barre, Maurine (Box 20)
  - La Barre, Weston (Box 20)
  - Lacy, Creighton [Divinity School] (Box 20)
  - Landon, Charles E. (Box 20)
  - Langford, Thomas [Divinity School] (Box 20)
  - Langley, John H. (Box 20)
  - Lanning, Johntate (Box 20)
  - La Prade, William Thomas (Box 20)
  - Larson, Arthur [School of Law] (Box 20)
  - Lassaw, Ibram (Box 20)
  - Latty, Elvin R. [School of Law] (Box 20)
  - Leach, James [With Margaret Mendenhall] (Box 20)
  - Leary, Lewis (Box 20)
  - Lee, Arthur Carl (Box 20)
  - Lee, Maurice W. (Box 20)
  - Leftwich, George E. "Jelly", 1977 [Band] (Box 20)
  - Leighton, Clare (Box 20)
  - Lemert, Ben (Box 20)
  - Leonard, Debbie (Box 20)
  - Leonard, Henry (Box 20)
  - Lester, Richard G. (Box 20)
  - Lewis, Harold (Box 20)
  - Lewis, Leroy (Box 20)
  - Liacouras, Peter (Box 20)
  - Lind, Fred (Box 20)
  - Linderoth, L.S. (Box 20)
  - Linebarger, Paul, M.A. (Box 20)
  - Linke, William R. (Box 20)
  - Livengood, Charles [Professor, School of Law] (Box 20)
  - Livesey, John (Box 20)
  - Lockwood, M.H. [Trick Photography] (Box 20)
  - London, Arthur (Box 20)
  - London, Fritz (Box 20)
  - Lovette, Al (Box 21)
  - Long, Johnny (Box 21)
  - Lowenbach, Hans (Box 21)
  - Lowndes, Charles L.B. (Box 21)
  - Lucas, Jack (Box 21)
  - Lumiansky, Robert (Box 21)
  - Lundeberg, O.K. (Box 21)
  - Lundholm, Helge (Box 21)
  - McAlister, Elizabeth (Box 21)
  - McBride, John (Box 21)
  - McCall, Adeline (Box 21)
  - McCall, Billy G. (Box 21)
  - McCaughan, Ralph [Class of 1961] (Box 21)
  - McClain, Joseph (Box 21)
  - McCloskey, Paul (Box 21)
  - McClure, Wallace (Box 21)
  - McDermott, Malcolm (Box 21)
  - McDonald, Alexander D. (Box 21)
  - McDougall, William (Box 21)
  - McDougall, William [Family] (Box 21)
  - McGeachy, Neill [Basketball Coach] (Box 21)
  - McGee, Mike (Michael B.) [Football Star and Coach, Includes Jerry McGee (Brother)] (Box 21)
  - McGough, Edward (Box 21)
  - McGovern, John P., M.D. (Box 21)
  - McGrath, Daniel (Box 21)
  - McHugh, Gelolo (Box 21)
  - McIntosh, Henry (Box 21)
  - McKay, John (Box 21)
  - McKay, Daisy (Box 21)
  - McKinney, John C. (Box 21)
  - McMahon, Alex (Box 21)
  - McWilliam, Stuart W. (Box 21)
  - Maddox, George (Box 21)
  - Maggs, Douglas (Box 21)
  - Maguire, Robert (Box 21)
  - Manchester, Alan K. (Box 21)
  - Mann, E.J. (Box 21)
  - Mann, Ted (Box 21)
  - Manry, James C. (Box 21)
  - Manschreck, Clyde (Box 21)
  - Marin, Jack (Box 21)
  - Markee, Joseph (Box 21)
  - Markham, Charles [Mayor of Durham] (Box 21)
  - Markham, Charles B. [Treasurer of Durham] (Box 21)
  - Markman, Sidney (Box 22)
  - Marshall, John [Chief Justice, Law School Portrait ] (Box 22)
  - Marshall, Roger (Box 22)
  - Martin, Donald S. (Box 22)
  - Massengill, Ray (Box 22)
  - Mattingly, Capitola (Box 22)
  - Maughan, William [Forestry] (Box 22)
  - Maytubby, Joseph Smith (Box 22)
  - Meier, Otto, Jr. (Box 22)
  - Menapace, John (Box 22)
  - Mengel, Charles (Box 22)
  - Menzel, David, M.D. (Box 22)
  - Menzies, Robert (Box 22)
  - Meyers, Eric and Carol (Box 22)
  - Miller, Justin (Box 22)
  - Miller, W. Starr (Box 22)
  - Mimms, Chris (Box 22)
  - Mims, Edwin (Box 22)
  - Minah, Theodore (Box 22)
  - Mitcham, C.L. (Box 22)
  - Mitchell, Fannie (Box 22)
  - Mohammed, Wallace D. (Box 22)
  - Moltmann, Jürgen (Box 22)
  - Monk, Thelonius [Jazz Institute, Publicity Photo] (Box 22)
  - Montague, Col. Ludwell Lee (Box 22)
  - Moore, Elizabeth Luci (Box 22)
  - Moore, Shelley [See also Capito, Shelley M.] (Box 22)
  - Mordecai, Sam F., Picture of Portrait (Box 22)
  - Moreland, Dr. (Box 22)
  - Mumford, L. Quincy (Box 22)
  - Moustakas, Evangelos (Box 22)
  - Mueller, Julia Wilkinson (Box 22)
  - Murphy, C.S. (Box 22)
  - Murphy, Roland [Divinity School] (Box 22)
  - Murray, William [Including Statue] (Box 22)
  - Myers, Hiram Earl (Box 22)
  - Meyers, Jack (Box 22)
  - Myers, George C. (Box 22)
  - Nader, Ralph, 1978 (Box 22)
  - Nasher, Ray [Class of 1943] (Box 22)
  - Naylor, Thomas (Box 22)
  - Nelson, Ernest William (Box 22)
  - Nelson, Norman (Box 22)
  - Nelson, Roland H. (Box 22)
  - Neurath, Hans (Box 22)
  - Newall, Isaac (Box 22)
  - Newbold, Nathan Carter (Box 22)
  - Newman, Gustave (Box 22)
  - Newsom, Dallas Walton (Box 23)
  - Newsome, Clarence G. [Divinity] (Box 23)
  - Nicholas, Peter M. [Chair, BOT, 2003-2005] (Box 23)
  - Nichols, Claude (Box 23)
  - Nicholson, William M. (Box 23)
  - Nicklas, Bruce (Box 23)
  - Nielsen, Walter (Box 23)
  - Nixon, Richard M. [Group Photos] (Box 23)
  - Nixon, Richard M., 1969 [Photos of Painting, Unveiling Presentation] (Box 23)
  - Nixon, Richard M., 1972 [Class Photos, Reunion Dinner at White House] (Box 23)
  - Nixon, Richard M. [Family, Julie N. Eisenhower at Duke] (Box 23)
  - Nixon, Richard M. [Posed Portraits] (Box 23)
  - Nixon, Richard M. [Residences in Durham] (Box 23)
  - Nolting, Jan (Box 23)
  - Nordheim, Lothar W. (Box 23)
  - Norfleet, Mrs. Del (Box 23)
  - North, W.C. (Box 23)
  - Novak, Richey (Box 23)
  - Nowlin, Dr. [Gerontology Mobile Unit] (Box 23)
  - Nuermberger, Ruth Ketring [Curator of Manuscripts, 1931-40] (Box 23)
  - Nurmi [See Shears, Randolf M.] (Box 23)
  - Oates, John F. (Box 23)
  - O'Barr, Jean (Box 23)
  - Obrist, Walter (Box 23)
  - Odell, W.R. (Box 23)
  - Odom, Guy L., M.D. (Box 23)
  - O'Neal, Forest Hodge (Box 23)
  - Oosting, H.J. (Box 23)
  - Ormond, Jesse M. (Box 23)
  - Ormandy, R.B. (Box 23)
  - Orr, Louis (Box 23)
  - Osborne, Bill (Box 23)
  - Osmond, C. Barry (Box 23)
  - Outler, Albert C. (Box 23)
  - Overman, John R. (Box 23)
  - Overman, Lee S. (Box 23)
  - Owen, Harry A. [Electrical Engineering] (Box 23)
  - Owens, Ida Virginia Stephens (Box 23)
  - Page, Walter H. [Original of Engraving in Special Collections] (Box 23)
  - Pardue, Len [University Relations] (Box 23)
  - Parker, Harold T. (Box 23)
  - Parker, John J. (Box 24)
  - Parker, Roy Turner, M.D. (Box 24)
  - Parrent, Allan (Box 24)
  - Paschal, Prof. [Law] (Box 24)
  - Patrick, Ben (Box 24)
  - Patrick, Ransome Rathbone (Box 24)
  - Patterson, Karl B. (Box 24)
  - Patterson, Robert Leet [Professor of Philosophy] (Box 24)
  - Patton, Dr. Lewis (Box 24)
  - Patton, William R. (Box 24)
  - Pearsall, George (Box 24)
  - Pearse, Arthur Sperry (Box 24)
  - Peele, Talmage Lee (Box 24)
  - Peele, William Walter (Box 24)
  - Pegram, William Howell (Box 24)
  - Penfield, Addison (Box 24)
  - Penrod, Kenneth E. (Box 24)
  - Pensak, Louis (Box 24)
  - Pepper, Joseph (Box 24)
  - Peppler, Charles W. [Classics, 1872-1953] (Box 24)
  - Perkins, Thomas L. (Box 24)
  - Perkins, William (Box 24)
  - Perlzweig (Box 24)
  - Perry, Edmund F. (Box 24)
  - Perry, Mr. Clifford (Box 24)
  - Perry, Francis (Box 24)
  - Perry, H.S. (Box 24)
  - Persons, Elbert L. (Box 24)
  - Persons, Elizabeth (Box 24)
  - Petry, Ray (Box 24)
  - Pfeiffer, Eric (Box 24)
  - Phelps, Jake (Box 24)
  - Phelps, Leland (Box 24)
  - Phillips, Dean Paula (Box 24)
  - Phillips, Jay (Box 24)
  - Philpott, Jane (Box 24)
  - Pickens, Marshall I (Box 24)
  - Pilkey, Orrin (Box 24)
  - Plimsoll, Sir James [Australian Ambassador] (Box 24)
  - Plyler, M.T. (Box 24)
  - Polanyi, Michael (Box 24)
  - Politano, Victor (Box 24)
  - Porter, Earl (Box 24)
  - Porter, F. Ross (Box 24)
  - Poston, Mary (Box 24)
  - Poteat, J. Douglas [School of Law] (Box 25)
  - Powell, Adam Clayton (Box 25)
  - Powell, Benjamin Edward (Box 25)
  - Powell, Benjamin Edward [Retirement Reception] (Box 25)
  - Powell, Virginia (Box 25)
  - Pratt, Ella Fountain (Box 25)
  - Pratt, J. Gaither [See also J.B. Rhine] (Box 25)
  - Pratt, Vernon (Box 25)
  - Predmore, Richard (Box 25)
  - Preiss, Jack (Box 25)
  - Preston, Richard (Box 25)
  - Price, David (Box 25)
  - Price, James (Box 25)
  - Price, Reynolds (Box 25)
  - Pride, Cletis (Box 25)
  - Proctor, Arthur M. (Box 25)
  - Proctor, J. Harris (Box 25)
  - Prothro, Tommy (Box 25)
  - Pye, A. Kenneth (Box 25)
  - Quinn, Louis (Box 25)
  - Rader, Melvin (Box 25)
  - Rahall, Nick (Box 25)
  - Raitt, Jill (Box 25)
  - Ralston, Charles William (Box 25)
  - Raney, Richard B. (Box 25)
  - Rankin, Robert S. (Box 25)
  - Rankin, W.W. (Box 25)
  - Rankin, Watson S. (Box 25)
  - Raper, Ed S. (Box 25)
  - Ratchford, Benjamin (Box 25)
  - Rauch, Henry (Box 25)
  - Ravitz, L.J. (Box 25)
  - Read, Frank T. [School of Law] (Box 25)
  - Reagan, Ronald, 1988 [Visit to Duke] (Box 25)
  - Reamer, I.T. (Box 25)
  - Reardon, Kenneth (Box 25)
  - Redding, Frances (Box 25)
  - Reed, F.J. (Box 25)
  - Reaves, Robert (Box 25)
  - Reichenberg-Hacket, Wally (Box 25)
  - Reiman, Donald (Box 25)
  - Reuben, Wilhelmina ("Mina") [See also "May Day" for negatives] (Box 25)
  - Rhine, Joseph B. [Experiments, See also Parapsychology] (Box 25)
  - Rhine, Joseph B. [Portraits, See also Parapsychology] (Box 25)
  - Rhoads, John M. (Box 26)
  - Rhyne, Charles Sylvanus (Box 26)
  - Ribicoff, Abraham (Box 26)
  - Richardson, Elliott (Box 26)
  - Richey, McMurry [Divinity School] (Box 26)
  - Rippy, J. Fred (Box 26)
  - Rivera, Rodolfo (Box 26)
  - Roalfe, William R. (Box 26)
  - Robbins, Jeffrey H. (Box 26)
  - Robert, Joseph C. (Box 26)
  - Roberts, J.H. (Box 26)
  - Robertson, Walter S. (Box 26)
  - Robinson, Charles K. [Divinity School] (Box 26)
  - Rockwell, Kenneth, M.D. (Box 26)
  - Rogers, Robert S. (Box 26)
  - Roll, W.G. (Box 26)
  - Rollins, Steed (Box 26)
  - Roosevelt, Theodore, 1905 [Southern Tour], Map Cabinet, Drawer 3 (Box 26)
  - Roosevelt, Mrs. Eleanor (Box 26)
  - Root, Paul Albert (Box 26)
  - Roper, Daniel C. (Box 26)
  - Ropp, Theodore (Box 26)
  - Ross, David [Development] (Box 26)
  - Ross, Robert A. (Box 26)
  - Rosse, Dr. [Anemia Feature] (Box 26)
  - Rothschild, Maurice de, 1990 [Cortes, Mauro] (Box 26)
  - Rowe, Gilbert (Box 26)
  - Rowe, Robert S. (Box 26)
  - Rudin, John J. (Box 26)
  - Rudisill, Mabel (Box 26)
  - Ruffin, J.M. (Box 26)
  - Rundles, Wayne, M.D. (Box 26)
  - Russell, Elbert (Box 26)
  - Russell, Mattie (Box 26)
  - Sabin, Albert B. (Box 26)
  - Sabiston, David Coston (Box 26)
  - Sabiston, Dr. [With Students] (Box 26)
  - Sales, R.H. (Box 26)
  - Salinger, Herman (Box 26)
  - Sandeen, Muriel I. (Box 26)
  - Sands, Alexander (Box 27)
  - Sanford, Margaret Rose (Box 27)
  - Sanford, Terry, 1970 [First Day as President] (Box 27)
  - Sanford, Terry [Group Photos], 2 folders (Box 27)
  - Sanford, Terry [Portraits] (Box 27)
  - Sanford, Terry [Inauguration] (Box 27)
  - Sanford, Terry [Inauguration, Winston-Salem Journal Photos] (Box 27)
  - Sanford, Terry, 1969 [Press Conference] (Box 27)
  - Sanford, Terry, 1985 [Retirement Party] (Box 27)
  - Sayegh, Fayez A. (Box 27)
  - Saylor, John (Box 27)
  - Scates, Douglas E. (Box 27)
  - Schaefer, Norb F. "Bud" (Box 27)
  - Schafer, Thomas A. (Box 27)
  - Schettler, Clarence (Box 27)
  - Schmidt-Nielsen, Knut (Box 27)
  - Schmidt-Nielsen, Bodil (Box 27)
  - Schlögl, John (Box 27)
  - Schiffman, Dr. Susan [Tasting Experiment] (Box 27)
  - Schock, Carl (Box 28)
  - Schumacher, Francis X. (Box 28)
  - Scott, Anne (Box 28)
  - Scott, Robert (Box 28)
  - Scott, William (Box 28)
  - Seeley, Walter J. (Box 28)
  - Seiker, Dr. Herbert O. (Box 28)
  - Semans, James Hustead (Box 28)
  - Semans, Mary Duke Biddle Trent (Box 28)
  - Sessoms, Stuart M. (Box 28)
  - Seversky, Alexander P. de (Box 28)
  - Seymour, Richard K. (Box 28)
  - Sharpe, John (Box 28)
  - Shears, Randolf M. [See also "Nurmi"] (Box 28)
  - Shelton, Dr. [NASA] (Box 28)
  - Shepard, Harold (Box 28)
  - Shields, John H. (Box 28)
  - Shimm, Melvin [School of Law] (Box 28)
  - Shipman, George A. (Box 28)
  - Shockley, Grant [Divinity School] (Box 28)
  - Shuman, R. Baird (Box 28)
  - Silverman, Albert S. (Box 28)
  - Sime, David (Box 28)
  - Simmons, Furnifold (Box 28)
  - Sindler, Allen (Box 28)
  - Singleton, Mary (Box 28)
  - Slaughter, Enos (Box 28)
  - Slaughter, Frank G. (Box 28)
  - Slay, James M. (Box 28)
  - Smeal, Eleanor Cutri (Box 28)
  - Smith, Carrington (Box 28)
  - Smith, David T. (Box 28)
  - Smith, Harmon [Divinity School] (Box 28)
  - Smith, Mrs. Hazen (Ruth Slack), circa 1928 [Associate Dean and Social Director] (Box 28)
  - Smith, Hilrie Shelton (Box 28)
  - Smith, J. Graham, Jr. (Box 28)
  - Smith, Dr. Joel [In office] (Box 28)
  - Smith, Robert S. (Box 28)
  - Smith, Susan Gower (Mrs. D.T.) (Box 28)
  - Smith, Willis (and family) [Chair of the Board of Trustees, 1946-53)] (Box 29)
  - Smullin, Frank (Box 29)
  - Sneed, Joseph T. (Box 29)
  - Snider, P.A. (Box 29)
  - Sockman, R.W. (Box 29)
  - Soong, Charles J. (Box 29)
  - Soper, Edmund Davison (Box 29)
  - Souchak, Mike [Football] (Box 29)
  - Southgate, James Haywood [President, Board of Trustees, 1897-1910] (Box 29)
  - Spanarkel, Jim (Box 29)
  - Sparks, Bertel [School of Law] (Box 29)
  - Spears, Estelle Flowers (Box 29)
  - Specter, Arlen (Box 29)
  - Spector, Benjamin (Box 29)
  - Spence, Bessie (Box 29)
  - Spence, Hersey Everett (Box 29)
  - Spaulding, Robert L. (Box 29)
  - Spengler, Joseph (Box 29)
  - Spengler, Dorothy K. (Mrs. J.J.) (Box 29)
  - Spielberger, Charles D. (Box 29)
  - Spock, Alexander (Box 29)
  - Sponer, Hertha (Box 29)
  - Spurrier, Steve (Box 29)
  - Stassen, Harold (Box 29)
  - St. John, Cirecel (Box 29)
  - Staddon, John [Psychology] (Box 29)
  - Stars, W.K. (Box 29)
  - Stead, Dr. Eugene (Box 29)
  - Stead and Wyngarten, 1968 (Box 29)
  - Stechow, Wolfgang (Box 29)
  - Stedman, Don (Box 29)
  - Steiner, Herman (Box 29)
  - Stephen, C.R. (Box 29)
  - Stern, William (Box 29)
  - Stevenson, Adlai (Box 29)
  - Stevenson, A.H. Lionel (Box 29)
  - Stinespring, William F. (Box 29)
  - Stoller, Morton J. (Box 30)
  - Stone, Dr. Donalde (Box 30)
  - Strobel, Howard Austin (Box 30)
  - Strowd, Elvin (Box 30)
  - Stumpf, W.A. (Box 30)
  - Styron, William (Box 30)
  - Sullivan, John D. [Forestry] (Box 30)
  - Swanson, Ernst W. (Box 30)
  - Sydnor, Charles Sackett (Box 30)
  - Taft, Robert A. (Box 30)
  - Tanford, Dr. (Box 30)
  - Taussig, Helen B. (Box 30)
  - Taylor, Grant (Box 30)
  - Taylor, Haywood (Box 30)
  - Taylor, Vince (Box 30)
  - Thiers, Ralph E. (Box 30)
  - Thant, U. (Box 30)
  - Thigpen, Richard Elton (Box 30)
  - Thomas, Anna Branson (Mrs. J.A.) (Box 30)
  - Thomas, James A. (Box 30)
  - Thomas, James Augustus [Memorial Celebration, See File under Events Reference Collection], 1962 (Box 30)
  - Thomas, Norman (Box 30)
  - Thomas, Walter (Box 30)
  - Thompson, Edgar T. (Box 30)
  - Thompson, Hunter S. (Box 30)
  - Tindall, John (Box 30)
  - Tipton, Eric [Football] (Box 30)
  - Tiryakian, Edward A. (Box 30)
  - Tischendorf, Alfred (Box 30)
  - Tisdale, Wright (Box 30)
  - Toren, Clifford (Box 30)
  - Tosteson, Daniel C. (Box 30)
  - Trent, Josiah C. (Box 30)
  - Troxell, Barbara (Box 30)
  - Trudeau, Pierre, 1974 [See Commencement 1974] (Box 30)
  - Trumbauer, Horace (Box 30)
  - Tucker, Gene (Box 30)
  - Turkington, Roger (Box 30)
  - Turner, Arlin [English Department] (Box 30)
  - Tuttle, Lee F. [Football] (Box 30)
  - Tutu, Bishop Desmond, 1986 [Republic of South Africa] (Box 30)
  - Tyler, Anne (Box 30)
  - Umstead, William B. (Box 30)
  - Upchurch, W.M., Jr. (Box 30)
  - Vacendak, Stephen T. (Box 30)
  - Vail, Charles R. (Box 30)
  - Van Alstyne, William [School of Law] (Box 30)
  - Vann, Arthur (Box 30)
  - Vanocur, Sander (Box 30)
  - Van Dusen, A.E. (Box 30)
  - Vasburgh, Warren C. (Box 30)
  - Vernsberg (Mr. and Mrs.) [Marine Lab] (Box 31)
  - Verwoerdt, Adrian (Box 31)
  - Vesic, Aleksandar (Box 31)
  - Vogel, Stephen (Box 31)
  - Vollmer, Clement (Box 31)
  - Volpp, Louis D. (Box 31)
  - Von Beckerath, Herbert (Box 31)
  - Von Canon, Fred (Box 31)
  - Wackerman, A.E. (Box 31)
  - Wade, Charles B. Jr. [Trustee] (Box 31)
  - Wade, Wallace, 2 folders (Box 31)
  - Wade, Wallace [Time Magazine Photo] (Box 31)
  - Wade, Wallace, 1967 [Wallace Wade Day, Stadium Naming] (Box 31)
  - Wade, Murray, Harp and Cameron, 1968 (Box 31)
  - Wade, Wallace and Knight, Doug, 1967 (Box 31)
  - Waggoner, Jake (Box 31)
  - Walbarsht, Myron (Box 31)
  - Wallace [School of Law] (Box 31)
  - Walters-Bugbee, Christopher [Divinity School] (Box 31)
  - Walton, A.J. (Box 31)
  - Walton, Loring B. (Box 31)
  - Wannamaker, William Hane [See also News Service Bio File] (Box 31)
  - Ward, Charles E. (Box 31)
  - Ward, James (Box 31)
  - Ward, Robert (Box 31)
  - Wardropper, Bruce (Box 31)
  - Warren, James V. (Box 31)
  - Warren, Robert Penn (Box 31)
  - Washington, Booker T. (Box 31)
  - Waters, R.C. (Bucky) (Box 31)
  - Watson, Karl Brantley (Box 31)
  - Watson, Richard Lyness, Jr. (Box 31)
  - Way, Kay (Box 31)
  - Weatherspoon, Everett B. (Box 31)
  - Webb, Albert M. (Box 31)
  - Weeks, Stephen Beauregard (Box 31)
  - Weitz, Henry (Box 31)
  - Welch, Frank E. [Faculty] (Box 31)
  - Welsh, Paul (Box 31)
  - Welty, Eudora (Box 31)
  - West, Alfred T. (Box 31)
  - Wetherby, Joseph (Box 31)
  - White, N.I. (Box 32)
  - White, Marie Updike (Box 32)
  - White, W.D. (Box 32)
  - Whitefield, Clarence (Box 32)
  - Whitener, Basil (Box 32)
  - Whitner, Fred (Box 32)
  - Whitford, William E. (Box 32)
  - Widgery, Alban G. (Box 32)
  - Wien, Janet (Box 32)
  - Wiesley with Wade [Practice Field] (Box 32)
  - Wilbur, Ralph S. (Box 32)
  - Wilder, Pelham (Box 32)
  - Wilkinson, Alice (Box 32)
  - Wilkinson, Howard C. (Box 32)
  - Williams, Mary Lou (Box 32)
  - Williams, Neil (Box 32)
  - Williamson, D.W. (Box 32)
  - Willis, William H. (Box 32)
  - Willkie, Wendell (Box 32)
  - Willson, A. Leslie (Box 32)
  - Wilson, A. Jack (Box 32)
  - Wilson, Florence K. (Box 32)
  - Wilson, Henry H. (Box 32)
  - Wilson, Mary Grace (Box 32)
  - Wilson, Nathan Hunt Daniel (Box 32)
  - Wilson, Robert L. (Box 32)
  - Wilson, Robert N. (Box 32)
  - Wilson, Robert R. (Box 32)
  - Wilson, Shirley "Red" (Box 32)
  - Wilson, Dr. William (Box 32)
  - Winkin, John [Basketball] (Box 32)
  - Winner, Thomas G. (Box 32)
  - Wintermute, Orval S. (Box 32)
  - Witherspoon, Jere W. (Box 32)
  - Wolfe, James Jacob (Box 32)
  - Wolslagel, Earl (Box 32)
  - Womble, B.S. (Box 32)
  - Womble, Hilburn (Box 32)
  - Wood, Don (Box 32)
  - Wood, Marquis Lafayette (Box 32)
  - Woodhall, Barnes (Box 32)
  - Woodring, Carl (Box 32)
  - Woodruff, Judy (Box 32)
  - Woods, Frank W. (Box 33)
  - Woody, Robert H. (Box 33)
  - Wright, Dean (Box 33)
  - Wright, Richard H. and Thomas D. (Box 33)
  - Yoho, James (Box 33)
  - York, Brantley (Box 33)
  - York, Brantley [Silhouette] (Box 33)
  - Young, Franklin (Box 33)
  - Young, Paul (Box 33)
  - Zener, Karl (Box 33)
- Activities Series, 44 Boxes, approx. 22,000 items
  - Admissions Office (Box 34)
  - Admissions Office, 1973 [Black Students. ABC] (Box 34)
  - Aesthetics, Art, and Music, Department of (Box 34)
  - A.F.R.O.T.C. (Box 34)
  - Allen Building Takeover [See: Demonstrations] (Box 34)
  - Fraternity: ATO (Box 34)
  - Alumnae Weekend (Box 34)
  - Alumnae and Alumni of Note (Box 34)
  - Alumnae Day, 1967 (Box 34)
  - Alumnae Weekend, 1968 (Box 34)
  - Alumni #1 (Box 34)
  - Alumni #2 (Box 34)
  - Alumni - Groups (Box 34)
  - Alumni Women, 1969 (Box 34)
  - Alumni Board (Box 34)
  - Alumni Class Agent Day, 1966 (Box 34)
  - Alumni Committees, 1972 (Box 34)
  - Alumni Divinity School (Box 34)
  - Anniversary, 50th, 1975 Apr. (Box 34)
  - Alumni (Box 35)
    - Engineering (Box 35)
    - Affairs Office (Box 35)
    - Half-Century Club (Box 35)
    - Individuals, Miscellaneous (Box 35)
    - Law School, Class of 1937 (Box 35)
    - Loyalty Fund (Box 35)
    - Medical Center (Box 35)
    - National Council Meet (Box 35)
    - School of Nursing (Box 35)
    - Weekend 1967, 1967 (Box 35)
    - Class Reunion Planning, 1971 (Box 35)
    - Summer Institute, 1977 (Box 35)
    - Washington Alumni Meeting with Knight (Box 35)
    - Weekend 1969 (Box 35)
    - Weekend #1, 1970 (Box 35)
    - Weekend #2, 1970 (Box 35)
    - Weekend, 1972 (Box 36)
    - Weekend, 1971 (Box 36)
    - Weekend, 1974 (Box 36)
    - Weekend, 1975 (Box 36)
    - School of Law, 1969, 1972 (Box 36)
    - Medical, 1970, 1971 (Box 36)
  - American Assembly Conference, 1961 (Box 36)
  - American Institute of Electrical Engineers (Box 36)
  - American Physical Society Meeting, 1953 (Box 36)
  - Angier B. Duke Scholars (Box 36)
  - Angier B. Duke Winners, 1959-1963 (Box 36)
  - Angier B. Duke Scholars Seminar, 1978 (Box 36)
  - Animal Research Facility (Box 36)
  - Archive, The (Publication (Box 36)
  - Armed Forces Day (Box 36)
  - Army Finance School (Box 37)
  - Army Research Office (Box 37)
  - Art, Department of (Box 37)
  - Art Museum (Brummer Collection) (Box 37)
  - Art Museum (Brummer Collection), 1968 (Box 37)
  - Art Museum - NC Artists Teachers Collection, 1975 (Box 37)
  - Art Museum - Exhibits (Box 37)
  - Artists Series [See Cultural Affairs Records] (Box 37)
  - Arts Council (Box 37)
  - A.S.D.U. (Box 37)
  - Athena (Women's Literary Society), 1920s (Box 37)
  - Athletics
    - Baseball [Trinity Park High School] (Box 37)
    - Baseball, 1931-1954 [Players ] (Box 37)
    - Baseball, 1896, 1897, 1898 [Teams], See also Trinity College Collection (Box 37)
    - Baseball, 1899, 1900 [Teams] (Box 37)
    - Baseball, 1903-1924 [Teams] (Box 37)